I think we need to talk about what it means to be a journalist.
I see a lot of people throwing the word journalist around all willy-nilly.
Journalist. Journalist. I am a journalist.
But I don't think we're really talking about what a journalist really is.
Or what a journalist really does.
A journalist identifies a story.
Then they do extensive research to prove it.
Then they synthesize it into a context that their readers can digest.
And if they're an ethical journalist, they do all of that in pursuit of the truth.
Now listen, some of us are out here and we're sharing stories.
We're interviewing folks. We're reading from prompters.
But we're not journalists.
We're essential. We're abrogators.
Advocates.
But we ain't journalists, baby.
We're journaling.